webgain.org 2002-12-09

# WebGain | Company : Privacy Statement

By registering with this web site, you agree to the terms and conditions (the "Terms") below. If you do not agree to these Terms, please do not use the web site or download any materials from it.

The materials on this web site (the "Site") are provided by WebGain for informational purposes only. These Terms will be revised from time to time. Please visit this page at least once every thirty days, to review any updates to the Terms. Your continued use of the Site shall be considered an acceptance of any revised Terms.

WebGain intends to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit WebGain on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may request information from you, such as your name and address so that we may correspond with you, process an order, send you trialware.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet, we will let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.

The WebGain site contains links to other Web sites. WebGain is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner. We will also periodically request that you update this information to ensure no disruption in important customer communications.

WebGain will implement technologies including "cookies" that are used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Please contact the webmaster if you have any questions or comments on this privacy statement.
